[{"question": " oh, ross, mon, is it okay if i bring someone to your parent&#146;s anniversary party?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " sure. yeah.", "answer": " so, who&#146;s the guy?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " well, his name is parker and i met him at the drycleaners.", "answer": " oooh, did he put a little starch in your bloomers?  who said that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " yeah, he&#146;s really great though. he has this incredible zest for life, and he treats me like a queen, except at night when he treats me like the naughty girl i am.", "answer": "  oh, by the way. would it be okay if i gave the toast to mom and dad this year?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " uh, yeah, you sure you want to after what happened at their 20th?", "answer": " yeah, i&#146;d really like to.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " okay, hopefully this time mom won&#146;t boo you.", "answer": " yes! every year ross makes the toast, and it&#146;s always really moving, and always makes them cry. well this year i&#146;m going to make them cry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " and you wonder why ross is their favorite?", "answer": " no! really! any time ross makes a toast everyone cries, and hugs him, and pats him on the back and they all come up to me and say, &quot;god, your brother.&quot; know what they&#146;ll say this year? &quot;god, you&quot;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " really you can do that?", "answer": " are you kidding me? watch!  well i can&#146;t do it with you guys watching me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " what are you doing?", "answer": " oh i&#146;m working on my toast for the party, or as i like to call it. sob fest 2002. hey check this out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " it&#146;s a dog.", "answer": " it&#146;s a dead dog. that&#146;s chi-chi; she died when i was in high school.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " it&#146;s your parents&#146; anniversary and you&#146;re going to talk about their dead pet?", "answer": " the good stuff, huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " you got a present for my parents. that&#146;s so sweet.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " yeah, yeah, in honor of their 35th wedding anniversary, i had a star named after them.", "answer": " aww that is so cool.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " and i got them a book on karma sutra for the elderly.", "answer": " hey, do you guys have any extra ribbon?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " yeah, sure. what do you need? we got lace, satin, sateen, raffia, gingham, felt,  and i think my testacles may be in here too.", "answer": "  aww! chi-chi! oh, i loved this dog! y&#146;know monica couldn&#146;t get braces because chi-chi needed knee surgery.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " you were the 200-pound 11-year-old who rode her!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " everybody, this is parker, parker this is&#133;", "answer": " no, no, no wait! don&#146;t tell me. let me guess.  joey, monica, ross, rachel and, i&#146;m sorry phoebe didn&#146;t mention you.  chandler, i&#146;m kidding all ready you&#146;re my favorite!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " ha!", "answer": " why don&#146;t all of you tell me a little about your self?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " ah, actually, i&#146;m sorry we-we probably should get going.", "answer": "  classic ross. rachel, rachel, oh how you glow. may i?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " i, uh, think you already are.", "answer": " rachel, you have life growing inside you. is there anything in this world more miraculous than&#151;oh a picture of a dog! whose is this?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " that&#146;s my old dog. he passed away years ago.", "answer": " oh well, at least you were lucky to have him. bow-wow old friend, bow-wow. so where&#146;s the party?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " it&#146;s out on the island. it&#146;s in massapequa.", "answer": " maaaassapequa, sounds like a magical place. tell me about massapequa, is it steep in native american history? {transcriber&#146;s note: interestingly alec baldwin was born in massapequa.}", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " well, there is an arby&#146;s in the shape of a tee-pee.", "answer": " okay, i got my note cards.  do you got the presents?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " and i&#146;ve got the car keys.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " we&#146;re driving!?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " so uh, he seems like a nice guy.", "answer": " yeah, yeah i like him a lot.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " ya wanna hang back and take our own cab?", "answer": " yeah, otherwise i&#146;m not going.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " hi", "answer": " hi!  hey mom.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " this is such a great party! 35 years. very impressive, do you guys have any pearls of wisdom?", "answer": " jack?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " that&#146;s a good question, dad. that&#146;s a good question&#133;", "answer": " hmmm&#133;.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": "  congratulations you two!", "answer": " thank you&#133;we&#146;re so excited", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " and also, congratulations on your wedding.", "answer": " wha&#151;what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " can we talk to you for just a y&#146;know&#133; it&#146;s just a little thing. well we think it&#146;s absolutely marvelous that you&#146;re having this baby out of wedlock, some of our friends are less open-minded. which is why we&#146;ve told them all that you&#146;re married. ross and rachel: what?!", "answer": " thanks for going along with this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " dad so what we have to pretend that we&#146;re married?", "answer": " son, i had to shave my ears for tonight. you can do this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " can you believe that?", "answer": " yeah, if you&#146;re going to do the ears, you might as well take a pass at the nosal area.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " no, us having to lie about being married.", "answer": " no, i know i don&#146;t either, but ya know what, it&#146;s their party, and it&#146;s just one night. and we don&#146;t even have to lie; we just won&#146;t say anything. if it comes up again, we&#146;ll just&#133;smile. we&#146;ll nod along.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " ross!", "answer": " rachel!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " hi aunt lisa, uncle dan", "answer": " congratulations on the baby, and on the wedding ross and rachel: hmmmm&#133;.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " oh&#133;", "answer": " so, how&#146;s married life treating you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": "  unbelievable!", "answer": " we love marriage!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " hey", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " i don&#146;t think the flash went off.", "answer": " dahaaa!  i&#146;m going to find the men&#146;s room, be right back.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " i&#146;ll go with you", "answer": " come on!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " somewhere there is someone with a tranquilizer gun and a huge butterfly net looking for that man.", "answer": " i have to go to the bathroom too, but i don&#146;t want him complimenting my thing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " i&#146;m so we weren&#146;t in the car! did he ever let up?", "answer": " he called the long island expressway a concrete miracle.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " were you guys making fun of parker?", "answer": " that depends, how much did you hear?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " so, he a little enthusiastic, what&#146;s wrong with that?", "answer": " it&#146;s just that, it&#146;s so much.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " i feel terrible.", "answer": " i know", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " open it! open it! open it!", "answer": " yeah baby!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " so we never got to hear about your wedding!", "answer": " we were surprise that we weren&#146;t invited.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " no, no, it was just our parents and 1 or 2 friends. it was a small wedding.", "answer": " but it was beautiful. i mean it was small, but kind of spectacular.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " where did you have it?", "answer": " on a cliff, in barbados, at sunset, and stevie wonder sang isn&#146;t she lovely as i walked down the aisle.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " really?", "answer": " yeah, stevie&#146;s an old family friend.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " oh my god. that sounds amazing. i would love to see pictures.", "answer": " so would i. you wouldn&#146;t think that annie liebawitz would forget to put film in the camera.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " would you excuse us for a second?  umm&#133;. what are you doing?", "answer": " what? i&#146;m not you. this may be the only wedding i ever have. i want it to be amazing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " okay, okay. ooooh, ooh maybe i rode in on a harley.", "answer": " okay, ross, it has to be realistic.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " are you okay? you seem kind of quiet.", "answer": " no, i&#146;m fine. i&#146;m great. i&#146;m with you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " and i&#146;m with you! what a great time to be alive! look at this plate-bouncy thing.  what an inspired solution to man&#146;s plate dispensing problems.", "answer": " hm huh, yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " ah! oysters! let me feed you one.", "answer": " no, that&#146;s not necessary.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " please.", "answer": " no, actually i don&#146;t eat&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " i won&#146;t quit until you try.", "answer": " okay, fine! fine!  mmm&#133;hmmmmm&#133;.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " what are they like? i&#146;ve never had one.", "answer": " why don&#146;t you just try one?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " what are you doin&#146;?", "answer": " just going over my toast. those two will never know what hit &#145;em. i can&#146;t wait. they&#146;re going to be crying so hard. they&#146;re going to be fighting for breath.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " and my veil was lace, made by blind, belgium nuns.", "answer": " blind?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " well, not at first, but it was very intricate work and they said even though they lost their sight, it was all worth it.", "answer": " i&#146;ll bet you looked beautiful&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " well, i don&#146;t know about that, but some said that i looked like a floating angel.", "answer": "  so, how did you propose?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " oh yeah. that&#146;s a great story.", "answer": " well, um, actually, i-i took her to the planetarium. that&#146;s-that&#146;s where we had our first date. um, she walked in and i had the room filled with lilies, her favorite flower&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " oh that is so sweet!", "answer": " shhh! i want to hear the rest!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " yeah uh, phoebe! look umm, i want to apologize about before, okay? we were being jerks. parker&#146;s a nice guy and i&#146;d like to get to know him.", "answer": " then you better do it now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " why?", "answer": " because i&#146;m going to kill him", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " what-what?", "answer": " you guys were right. he&#146;s just too excited about&#133;everything. i mean i&#146;m all for living life, but this is the geller&#146;s 35th anniversary. okay? let&#146;s call a spade a spade this party stinks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " i know i&#146;m having the worst time. there was a 15-minute line for the buffet, and when i finally got up to the plates, i slipped on a giant booger!", "answer": " are you sure it wasn&#146;t an oyster?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " i guess it could&#146;ve been, i didn&#146;t really look at it. y&#146;know, i just wiped it on chandler&#146;s coat and got the hell out of there.", "answer": " he&#146;s just such a great guy i&#146;m so excited about him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " oh hey, you should be excited about him. there&#146;s nothing wrong with him he&#146;s a good guy.", "answer": " you think?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " yeah. ya know what i think; i think we were all just being too negative.", "answer": " you&#146;re right. you&#146;re right, he&#146;s just embracing life. we could all stand to be a little more like parker. you know what? i am like him! i&#146;m a sunny, positive person.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " actually, you have a little bit of an edge.", "answer": " what&#146;s that now?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " nothing&#133;", "answer": " oh look it&#146;s parker!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " look! it&#146;s the bunny hop!", "answer": " oooh i love it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " you do?!", "answer": " are you kidding? people acting like animals to music. come on!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " no, no it&#146;s going to be great. really! mom, dad, when i got married, one of the things that made me sure i could do it was the amazing example the two of you set for me. for that and so many other things i want to say thank you. i know i probably don&#146;t say it enough, but i love you.  when i look around this room, i&#146;m-i&#146;m saddened by the thought of those who could not be here with us. nana, my beloved grandmother who would so want to be here, but she can&#146;t because she&#146;s dead. as is our dog chi-chi. i mean look how cute she is. . was.  do me a favor and pass this to my parents. remember she&#146;s dead. okay, her and nana, gone. wow! hey does anybody remember when debra winger had to say goodbye to her children in terms of endearment?  didn&#146;t see that? no movie fans?! you want to hear something sad? the other day i was watching 60 minutes these orphans in romania, who have been so neglected, they were incapable of love.  you people are made of stone! here&#146;s to mom and dad! whatever!", "answer": " thank you monica that was uh, interesting. wasn&#146;t it interesting, jack?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": "  why don&#146;t i remember this dog?", "answer": " ross, why don&#146;t you give us your toast now?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " oh, no, mom, it&#146;s just monica this year.", "answer": " you&#146;re not going to say anything? on our 35th wedding anniversary", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " no, of course, um&#133; um, everybody? um, i-i just wanted to say&#133;on behalf of my new bride, rachel , and myself. umm, that if&#133;if in 35 years, we&#146;re half as happy as you guys are, we&#146;ll count ourselves the luckiest people in the world.", "answer": "  oh ross&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " my god what a fantastically well lit hallway!", "answer": " can i get you something to drink? like a water and valium?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " i must say this apartment, its, its, there are no words&#133;", "answer": " oh thank god.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " it&#146;s a haven. a third-floor paradise. a modern-day eden in the midst&#133;", "answer": " yeah? i know! i know! uh huh? listen why don&#146;t we just um, sit and relax? you know just be with each other. quietly!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " let&#146;s try something else, let&#146;s play a game.", "answer": " i love games!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " or&#133;jenga.", "answer": " but, let&#146;s play this one first. and remember whoever talks first loses!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " i lose, now jenga.", "answer": " oh my god! oh my god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " is something wrong?", "answer": " wrong? really? you know the word wrong. everything isn&#146;t perfect? everything isn&#146;t magical? everything isn&#146;t a glow with the light of a million fairies? they were just brake lights, parker!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " well, excuse me for putting a good spin on a traffic jam!", "answer": " you don&#146;t have to put a good spin on everything.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " i&#146;m sorry that&#146;s who i am. i&#146;m a positive person.", "answer": " no! i am a positive person. you are like santa clause on prozac, at disneyland, getting laid!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " so what do you want me to do, you want me to be more negative, less happy?", "answer": " much less happy!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " fine! well then to quote ross, &quot;i&#146;d better be going.&quot;", "answer": " so long! don&#146;t let the best door in the world hit you in the ass on your way out!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " isn&#146;t this the most incredible fight you&#146;ve ever had in your entire life?", "answer": " uh huh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " &#133;and then, we could&#146;ve gone from the ceremony to the reception with you in the sidecar!", "answer": " ross, it just wouldn&#146;t have been feasible.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " but having a dove place the ring on your finger would&#146;ve been no problem?", "answer": " it was really fun being married to you tonight.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " yeah! and! and, it was the easiest 400 bucks i&#146;ve ever made.", "answer": " okay ross, can i uh, can i ask you something?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " that proposal, at the planetarium&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " i know, i know it was stupid.", "answer": " are you kidding?! with the, with the lilies, and-and the song, and the stars! it was&#133;really wonderful! did you just make that up?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " no, actually i thought about it when, when we were going out. it&#146;s how i imagined i uh, i would ask you to marry me.", "answer": " well, that would&#146;ve been very hard to say no too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " it&#146;s a good thing i didn&#146;t do it, because it sounds like it would&#146;ve been a very expensive wedding.  okay, good night", "answer": " goodnight", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " even if the sidecar had a windscreen so your hair wouldn&#146;t get messed up?", "answer": " i will think about it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " okay that&#146;s it. i give up. at mom and dad&#146;s 40th anniversary, you&#146;re the one giving the speech.", "answer": " y&#146;know i don&#146;t understand why they didn&#146;t cry. it was a beautiful speech.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " oh, come on.", "answer": " hey! all that stuff you said about true love, you were right, i mean, we did learn a lot from mom and dad! and that picture of chi-chi with her mischievous grin. and what you said about nana. ohh, yeah she really would&#146;ve wanted to be there. and you know what? i think she was.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}]